Jonatan Schultz

Date of birth: 28/09/1996 Nationality: Swedish Address: Jönköping, Sweden

Phone number: +46768378327

Email address: jonatan_schultz@hotmail.com





♣ Profile

I am a system developer with big passion for technology. I have a continuous desire to learn new methods of working, and new ways of thinking. I am a passionate leader and strive to bring to the best out of my colleagues.

- 1 Year experience in dotnet.
- 1 Year experience in QA

Two years of experience with React, TypeScript, NextJs.

1 Year experience Project coordinator & Team Lead system development

Work Experience

₩ 09/2018 - 2020 O BORÅS, SWEDEN

Deviation Handler Speed Competence AB

- Manage the WorkFlow Management System
- · Keep track of deviations
- Use system SAP to handle orders and warehouse management.

 ➡ 11/2020 - 03/2022
 ♦ SVENLJUNGA, SWEDEN

System developer Blåkläder AB

Full-Stack development using C#, TypeScript, NodeJs, React, NextJs, Azure services and more.

Quality Assurance & Testing

📛 03/2022 - PRESENT 🥎 SVENLJUNGA, SWEDEN

System Developer & Team Lead Blåkläder AB

- Scrum Master
- Coordinate project & resource planning
- Analyzed user requirements
- Wrote code to run software
- · Tested system to ensure correct functioning
- Manage Release & Deployments

Education

Education

苗 09/2019 - 06/2021 🕥 BORÅS, SWEDEN

Systemutveckling .NET Borås Yrkeshögskola

.NET Development, Web development, Databases, Application development, Project methodology, Full-Stack

I Skills

(i) LANGUAGES

Swedish Native
English Full
Mandarin Limited
Spanish Limited

(i) PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

C#
TypeScript
CSS
HTML
SQL
XAML

(i) TOOLS AND FRAMEWORKS

Azure

REST

GIT

Agile

React

Docker

NodeJS

Publications

jonatanschultz.com

jonatanschultz.com

Social Media





@jonatan-schultz

@exemplarisk